webuzo.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy

---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  

Our Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Information Collected By Us  This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Softaculous website or forums. When you register on Softaculous Websites / Forums, we will ask you to provide personal information. We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our sites and services to offer a personalized experience. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name
  * Address 
  * Email address 

How We Use Information  We use the information we collect to provide the services you request. We use your information to inform you of other products or services offered by Softaculous Inc. and to send you relevant survey invitations related to our services. We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists to third parties.

Our Commitment To Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

How To Access Or Correct Your Information  You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online.  
You can change information by accessing your User Control Panel and editing the same.  
You can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

Limitation of Liability Complete confidentiality over the Internet is not yet possible. It is possible for a third party to view the information you provide while registering on our sites. You acknowledge and agree that Softaculous Inc. shall not be responsible for any damages you may suffer as a result of the transmission of confidential or sensitive information over the Internet, and that all such communications will be at your own risk.

How To Contact Us Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [support@softaculous.com](mailto:support@softaculous.com).

Softaculous Inc. reserves the right to update and amend this policy as it is deemed necessary or appropriate to do so. We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Softaculous Inc. is protecting your information.

Links

Experience it!

Tools

Information

Get in touch

Blogs

---|---|---|---|---|---  
© 2015 [Softaculous Ltd.](http://www.softaculous.com/)    All trademarks and logos are the property of their respective owners!
